Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Gorgeous Dream=
=حلم رائع=
(Adapted from the novel "The Charming Evil Consort")
(مقتبس من رواية "الزوجة الشريرة الساحرة")
=Episode 17=
=الحلقة 17=
Miss Lan.
السيدة لان.
(Graceful and Poised)
(رشيقة ومتوازنة)
(Chinese New Year's Eve, tattoo under eyes)
(ليلة رأس السنة الصينية، وشم تحت العينين)
(Tattoo under eyes)
(وشم تحت العين)
(Yang Wei)
(يانغ وي)
(Found him.)
(وجدته.)
Peaceful, peaceful, peaceful.
سلمية، سلمية، سلمية.
Search this room.
ابحث في هذه الغرفة.
At this late hour,
في هذه الساعة المتأخرة،
where exactly has Miss Lan gone?
أين ذهبت الآنسة لان بالضبط؟
What if something dangerous happens?
ماذا لو حدث شيء خطير؟
Lady Lan.
السيدة لان.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Mo.
ل.
You've lost weight, Mo.
لقد فقدت الوزن، مو.
- You've lost weight. - Lady Lan.
- لقد فقدت الوزن. - ليدي لان.
Mo.
ل.
Lady Lan.
السيدة لان.
It's not Mo.
إنه ليس مو.
It's the little stray cat in the bureau, called Mei.
إنها القطة الضالة الصغيرة في المكتب، تدعى مي.
It is Mo.
إنه مو.
When I was sleeping today,
عندما كنت نائما اليوم،
it climbed into my bed.
لقد صعد إلى سريري.
It's Mo.
إنه مو.
Mo came to find me.
لقد جاء مو ليجدني.
Right, Mo?
يمينًا، مو؟
So you chased it all the way here?
فهل طاردته طوال الطريق إلى هنا؟
- Mo. - Lady Lan.
-أنتِ. - ليدي لان.
It really isn't Mo.
إنه ليس مو حقا.
If it was, how could it scratched you?
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فكيف يمكن أن يخدشك؟
It is Mo.
إنه مو.
It is.
إنها.
Mo, no matter what you become,
مو، بغض النظر عما تصبح عليه،
I will always love you, okay?
سأحبك دائمًا، حسنًا؟
Look, the moon is so full tonight.
انظر، القمر مكتمل الليلة.
Let's watch the first ray of sunlight together.
دعونا نشاهد أول شعاع من ضوء الشمس معًا.
I understand the pain of longing.
أنا أفهم ألم الشوق.
Lady Lan.
السيدة لان.
Why don't you come down first?
لماذا لا تنزل أنت أولاً؟
Tomorrow I will talk to you.
سأتحدث معك غدا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
What does it mean that you pushed me away?
ماذا يعني أنك دفعتني بعيدا؟
Mo.
ل.
- Mo, I missed you so much. - Lady Lan.
- مو، لقد افتقدتك كثيرًا. - ليدي لان.
Mo.
ل.
(Holding Pearls and Jade)
(يحمل اللؤلؤ واليشم)
Do you feel any discomfort?
هل تشعر بأي إزعاج؟
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
You don't even know that you are sick.
أنت لا تعرف حتى أنك مريض.
What do you mean by this, Ms. Tong?
ماذا تقصدين بهذا يا آنسة تونغ؟
I have always been healthy.
لقد كنت بصحة جيدة دائمًا.
I guess your sense of pain is gone.
أعتقد أن إحساسك بالألم قد ذهب.
Last night
ليلة أمس
was a sign that your mind was collapsing.
كانت علامة على أن عقلك كان ينهار.
I just tolerate pain better than most people.
أنا فقط أتحمل الألم بشكل أفضل من معظم الناس.
Is that a disease?
هل هذا مرض؟
The root of your illness
جذر مرضك
is not in the body,
ليس في الجسم،
but in the mind.
ولكن في العقل.
You desire something you cannot have
أنت ترغب في شيء لا يمكنك الحصول عليه
and it turns into obsession.
ويتحول إلى هوس.
Obsession is like poison.
الهوس مثل السم
If unresolved for a day,
إذا لم يتم حلها لمدة يوم واحد،
it erodes your senses day and night,
إنه يؤدي إلى تآكل حواسك ليلًا ونهارًا،
turning you into someone who feels no pain,
تحويلك إلى شخص لا يشعر بالألم،
a monster without emotions or desires.
وحش بلا مشاعر أو رغبات.
Monster?
وحش؟
Is there anything wrong with following your path?
هل هناك أي خطأ في اتباع طريقك؟
Is it wrong?
هل هذا خطأ؟
Following your path is not wrong.
إتباع طريقك ليس خطأ.
However,
لكن،
what waxes must wane.
ما يشمع لابد أن يتضاءل.
If you indulge in obsession,
إذا انغمست في الهوس،
and feed your inner demons,
وتغذي شياطينك الداخلية،
you will gradually lose sight
سوف تفقد البصر تدريجيا
of whether what you see is a demon,
هل ما تراه هو شيطان،
or your own reflection.
أو انعكاسك الخاص.
If this continues, one day,
إذا استمر هذا الأمر يومًا ما،
you will become
سوف تصبح
a monster nurtured by your inner demons.
وحش تغذيه شياطينك الداخلية.
And then...
وثم...
You
أنت
will still be you?
هل ستظل أنت؟
Rest here for a while.
إرتاح هنا لفترة من الوقت.
(These years,)
(هذه السنوات)
(I've been planning every day,)
(لقد كنت أخطط كل يوم)
(and driven by obsession.)
(وتدفعها الهوس.)
(Is it really wrong?)
(هل هذا خطأ حقا؟)
(This time I must first find)
(هذه المرة يجب أن أجد أولاً)
(the man with the tattoo on his face)
(الرجل ذو الوشم على وجهه)
(before talking about letting go of obsession.)
(قبل أن نتحدث عن التخلص من الهوس.)
Miss Lan, my name is Yin.
السيدة لان، اسمي يين.
(Jade Spy Bureau officer, Yin) Ms. Tong asked me to take care of you.
(ضابط مكتب تجسس اليشم، يين) طلبت مني السيدة تونغ أن أعتني بك.
To let go,
للتخلي عنها
but now is not the time.
ولكن الآن ليس الوقت المناسب.
(Chinese New Year's Eve, tattoo under eyes)
(ليلة رأس السنة الصينية، وشم تحت العينين)
Yin.
عمل.
Do you know that in our bureau
هل تعلم أنه في مكتبنا
there is a servant named Yang Wei?
هناك خادم اسمه يانغ وي؟
Indeed, there is a servant named Yang Wei.
في الواقع، هناك خادم اسمه يانغ وي.
Could you take me to see him?
هل يمكن أن تأخذني لرؤيته؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Look. Is this the one?
انظر، هل هذا هو؟
(Jade Spy Bureau coachman, Yang Wei)
(مدرب مكتب جايد للتجسس، يانغ وي)
Who are you?
من أنت؟
(Not him.)
(ليس هو.)
Have you ever been to Ning City
هل سبق لك زيارة مدينة نينغ؟
and met a man named Chen Huanfeng?
وأيضا رجل يدعى تشين هوانفينج؟
(Jade Spy Bureau coachman, Yang Wei) I have been to Ning City.
(سائق مكتب تجسس اليشم، يانغ وي) لقد زرت مدينة نينغ.
Who do you mean?
من تقصد؟
About this tall,
حول هذا الطول،
left-handed.
عسراء.
That strange man.
هذا الرجل الغريب.
He gave me 50 taels of silver
لقد أعطاني 50 تايل من الفضة
and asked me to chat with him.
وطلب مني أن أتحدث معه.
He said chat,
وقال الدردشة،
but he never spoke to me.
ولكنه لم يتحدث معي أبدًا.
Always staring out the window,
دائما أتطلع من النافذة،
sat like that for two hours.
جلست هكذا لمدة ساعتين.
Then he left.
ثم غادر.
(Could it be Chen Huanfeng)
(هل يمكن أن يكون تشن Huanfeng)
(has long noticed the spies around him,)
(لاحظ منذ فترة طويلة الجواسيس من حوله)
(and deliberately set us up?)
(وتعمدوا إعدادنا؟)
(Now the clues are gone.)
(الآن اختفت الأدلة.)
(Could it be fate?)
(هل يمكن أن يكون القدر؟)
(I am ultimately trapped by obsession.)
(أنا في نهاية المطاف محاصر بالهوس.)
(Have I taken the wrong path?)
(هل اتخذت الطريق الخطأ؟)
Miss Lan, are you alright?
آنسة لان، هل أنت بخير؟
Miss Lan.
السيدة لان.
I don't know what happened to you.
لا أعلم ماذا حدث لك.
But everything will be fine.
ولكن كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام.
The Jade Spy Bureau people bullied you?
هل قام أفراد مكتب التجسس في جايد بتنمر عليك؟
No.
لا.
It was the Jade Spy Bureau who saved me.
لقد كان مكتب التجسس اليشم هو الذي أنقذني.
I used to beg on the streets
كنت أتسول في الشوارع
and blocked a noble's path,
وسدّ طريق النبيل،
almost beaten to death by the noble's servants.
كاد أن يتعرض للضرب حتى الموت على يد خدم النبيل.
Jade Spy Bureau saved me,
لقد أنقذني مكتب تجسس جاد،
treated my wounds
عالج جروحي
and gave me enough food.
وأعطوني ما يكفي من الطعام.
Have you ever thought
هل فكرت يوما
to make those nobles pay?
لجعل هؤلاء النبلاء يدفعون الثمن؟
At first,
في البداية،
I had nightmares every night.
لقد كان لدي كوابيس كل ليلة.
In the dream, I was starving to death
في الحلم كنت أموت من الجوع
or beaten to death.
أو ضرب حتى الموت.
Ms. Tong told me
قالت لي السيدة تونغ
that these are nightmare beasts born of obsession.
أن هذه هي الوحوش الكابوسية المولودة من الهوس.
Thanks to Ms. Tong,
شكرًا للسيدة تونغ،
she made this protective doll for me.
لقد صنعت لي هذه الدمية الواقية.
As long as I wear it,
طالما أرتديه،
I can sleep through the night.
أستطيع النوم طوال الليل.
Soon Ms. Tong will send me to the embroidery workshop to learn skills.
قريبا سوف ترسلني السيدة تونغ إلى ورشة التطريز لتعلم المهارات.
When I learn,
عندما أتعلم،
I will make a protective doll for you too.
سأصنع لك دمية واقية أيضًا.
Lan Mengyan.
لان منجيان.
I will never allow anyone
لن اسمح لأحد أبدا
to ruin the good name of the Liu family!
لتدمير سمعة عائلة ليو الطيبة!
Qing!
تشينغ!
Qing, why are you only here now?
تشينغ، لماذا أنت هنا الآن فقط؟
I thought you abandoned me too.
اعتقدت أنك تخليت عني أيضًا.
(Obsession has deepened.)
(لقد أصبح الهوس أعمق.)
(Lost sense of pain.)
(فقدت الإحساس بالألم.)